<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upcoming shows on Income Tax Refund</title><link>https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/</link><description>Recent content in Upcoming shows on Income Tax Refund</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anna Lucia + Julia Witas</title><link>https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/2024-09-20/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 11:12:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/2024-09-20/</guid><description>ITR &amp;amp; PR__HT present:
20 Sept 2024
doors 20h00
startttt 20h30
Anna Lucia
»&amp;hellip;is a Berlin-based musician and artist who works at the intersection of music, performance and visual arts. Centered around a magnetic vocal delivery, she fuses elements of poetry, film-score and drone into ecstatic pop dirges that oscillate between hope and despair and allow dark and powerful moments to co-exist with passages of fragility and softness. Through her lyrics she channels characters; playing with the audience&amp;rsquo;s perspectives and expectations using a method of alternative storytelling, which dips anachronistically in and out of different histories, both imagined and real.</description></item><item><title>Rắn Cạp Đuôi + syw</title><link>https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/2024-07-23/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 11:12:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/2024-07-23/</guid><description>ITR presents:
23 July, 2024
@ TV Studio Ost
doors 19h30
startttt 20h00
Rắn Cạp Đuôi (free electronic noise rock / Ho Chi Minh City)
Rắn Cạp Đuôi is a collective of the Vietnamese artist Đỗ Tấn Sĩ, Phạm Thế Vũ, Zach Sch, Đỗ Hoàng Tuấn Anh, and Vuong Thien doing unexpected noise rock mayhem, glitched-out bracing DJ sets, captivating situanist performances and all that. They have released on Subtext Recordings and are part of Gãy collective from Sài Gòn.</description></item><item><title>Marius Atherton + Gelbart + OORT CLOUD</title><link>https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/2024-07-05/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 11:12:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://marvelous-crostata-5e7f99.netlify.app/upcoming/2024-07-05/</guid><description>Next ITR show!!!
date: fri, 5th july 2024
doors: 19h30
start: 20h00
MARIUS ATHERTON/ baroque synth ballads, paris
beachy, brill tunes by this ex-Stratocastors member
BC // insta
GELBART / experimental analog computer pop, bln
space age techno, befittingly released on Joyful Noise and Gagarin Records among others
bc // insta // tecno
OORT CLOUD / squeak rock, ch
experiments at the edge between new music, noise, rock and improvisation</description></item></channel></rss>